let questionsAndAnswers = [
    {
        question: "Who is the all-time Premier League top scorer?",
        a: "Wayne Rooney",
        b: "Alan Shearer",
        c: "Mohammed Salah",
        d: "Harry Kane",
        correctAnswer: "b",
    },
    {
        question: "Which team has the most Premier League titles?",
        a: "Chelsea",
        b: "Arsenal",
        c: "Manchester United",
        d: "Manchester City",
        correctAnswer: "c",
    },
    {
        question: "Who has the most assists in Premier League history?",
        a: "Ryan Giggs",
        b: "Steven Gerrard",
        c: "Thierry Henry",
        d: "Trent Alexander-Arnold",
        correctAnswer: "a",
    },
    {
        question: "How many teams have won the Premier League?",
        a: "5",
        b: "6",
        c: "7",
        d: "8",
        correctAnswer: "c",
    },
    {
        question: "What is the record points total in a Premier League season?",
        a: "100",
        b: "114",
        c: "106",
        d: "98",
        correctAnswer: "a",
    },
    {
        question: "Who has the most Premier League appearances?",
        a: "Mark Noble",
        b: "Ryan Giggs",
        c: "David James",
        d: "Gareth Barry",
        correctAnswer: "d",
    },
    {
        question: "In what year did the Premier League begin?",
        a: "1990",
        b: "1995",
        c: "1992",
        d: "1996",
        correctAnswer: "c",
    },
    {
        question: "Who has played for the most Premier League clubs?",
        a: "Nicolas Anelka",
        b: "Craig Bellamy",
        c: "Marcus Bent",
        d: "Andy Cole",
        correctAnswer: "c",
    },
    {
        question: "Which player has not won the Premier League with two different clubs?",
        a: "Frank Lampard",
        b: "Robert Huth",
        c: "Henning Berg",
        d: "Ashley Cole",
        correctAnswer: "a",
    },
    {
        question: "Which of these teams have been relegated from the Premier league?",
        a: "Everton",
        b: "Tottenham Hotspur",
        c: "Manchester City",
        d: "Chelsea",
        correctAnswer: "c",
    }
];

let quiz = document.getElementById('quiz');
let answers = document.getElementsByClassName('answer');

